<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Caroline Begg on TreeGuard AI</title><link>https://carolinebegg.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-autodeployed/authors/caroline-begg/</link><description>Recent content in Caroline Begg on TreeGuard AI</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>Caroline Begg</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 05:46:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://carolinebegg.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-autodeployed/authors/caroline-begg/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>TreeGuard AI's Value Proposition</title><link>https://carolinebegg.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-autodeployed/post/value-proposition/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://carolinebegg.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-autodeployed/post/value-proposition/</guid><description>TreeGuard AI&amp;rsquo;s Value Proposition Leveraging deep learning techniques and thousands of ecological data sets to create precise mappings of the terrain.
AI-Powered, Eco-Inspired.
Existing Problems Within Construction Surveying Challenge Terrain with Complex Landforms Crafting a Detail Conceptual Site Model Long Wait Times To Obtain A Building Permit TreeGuard&amp;rsquo;s cutting-edge tech uses satellite imagery and artificial intelligence to streamline land surveys, offering detailed mappings and 3D models, which expedites the permitting, planning, and building processes.</description></item><item><title>Technology Behind TreeGuard AI</title><link>https://carolinebegg.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-autodeployed/post/technology-behind-treeguard/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://carolinebegg.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-autodeployed/post/technology-behind-treeguard/</guid><description>Technology Behind TreeGuard AI The idea for TreeGuard was first inspired by an article about team of researchers at NASA who utilized satellite imagery and artificial intelligence to chart billions of individual tree crowns, allowing them to obtain an extremely accurate and precise mapping of many of the North African terrain. Employing allometric equations from earlier tree samplings, the researchers were then able translate these images into quantifiable estimates of tree biomass, including wood, foliage, roots, and their carbon sequestration capabilities.</description></item><item><title>What Is TreeGuard AI?</title><link>https://carolinebegg.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-autodeployed/post/what-is-treeguard/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://carolinebegg.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-autodeployed/post/what-is-treeguard/</guid><description>What Is TreeGuard AI? This semester, I am taking the class MGMT 2760 (Entrepreneurship and Technological Innovation), which is Wharton Management class that is part of the Entrepreneurship and Innovation concentration and the Engineering Entrepreneurship minor. As part of the final project for this class, we had to choose a novel technology on which to build an entrepreneurial firm and describe the value that the firm would bring to what customers and users.</description></item><item><title>Docs</title><link>https://carolinebegg.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-autodeployed/page/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://carolinebegg.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-autodeployed/page/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Posts</title><link>https://carolinebegg.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-autodeployed/post/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://carolinebegg.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-autodeployed/post/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>