<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>TreeGuard AI</title><link>https://carolinebegg.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/</link><description>Recent content on TreeGuard AI</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>Caroline Begg</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 04:14:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://carolinebegg.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>TreeGuard AI's Value Proposition</title><link>https://carolinebegg.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/post/value-proposition/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://carolinebegg.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/post/value-proposition/</guid><description>TreeGuard AI&amp;rsquo;s Value Proposition Leveraging deep learning techniques and thousands of ecological data sets to create precise mappings of the terrain.
AI-Powered, Eco-Inspired.
Existing Problems Within Construction Surveying Challenge Terrain with Complex Landforms Crafting a Detail Conceptual Site Model Long Wait Times To Obtain A Building Permit TreeGuard&amp;rsquo;s cutting-edge tech uses satellite imagery and artificial intelligence to streamline land surveys, offering detailed mappings and 3D models, which expedites the permitting, planning, and building processes.</description></item><item><title>Technology Behind TreeGuard AI</title><link>https://carolinebegg.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/post/technology-behind-treeguard/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://carolinebegg.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/post/technology-behind-treeguard/</guid><description>Technology Behind TreeGuard AI The idea for TreeGuard was first inspired by an article about team of researchers at NASA who utilized satellite imagery and artificial intelligence to chart billions of individual tree crowns, allowing them to obtain an extremely accurate and precise mapping of many of the North African terrain. Employing allometric equations from earlier tree samplings, the researchers were then able translate these images into quantifiable estimates of tree biomass, including wood, foliage, roots, and their carbon sequestration capabilities.</description></item><item><title>What Is TreeGuard AI?</title><link>https://carolinebegg.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/post/what-is-treeguard/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://carolinebegg.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/post/what-is-treeguard/</guid><description>What Is TreeGuard AI? This semester, I am taking the class MGMT 2760 (Entrepreneurship and Technological Innovation), which is Wharton Management class that is part of the Entrepreneurship and Innovation concentration and the Engineering Entrepreneurship minor. As part of the final project for this class, we had to choose a novel technology on which to build an entrepreneurial firm and describe the value that the firm would bring to what customers and users.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://carolinebegg.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://carolinebegg.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/about/</guid><description>About Us Made with ❤️ by the Hugo Bootstrap Theme team.</description></item><item><title>Code of Conduct</title><link>https://carolinebegg.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/code-of-conduct/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://carolinebegg.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/code-of-conduct/</guid><description>Contributor Covenant Code of Conduct Our Pledge We as members, contributors, and leaders pledge to make participation in our community a harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of age, body size, visible or invisible disability, ethnicity, sex characteristics, gender identity and expression, level of experience, education, socio-economic status, nationality, personal appearance, race, caste, color, religion, or sexual identity and orientation.
We pledge to act and interact in ways that contribute to an open, welcoming, diverse, inclusive, and healthy community.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://carolinebegg.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://carolinebegg.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/contact/</guid><description>Contact Please feel free to reach out with any questions, comments, or concerns.
Name: Caroline Begg
University: University of Pennsylvania
School: Wharton/SEAS (M&amp;amp;T)
Year: Sophomore
Major: Computer Science, Finance/Business Analytics
School Email: cbegg@wharton.upenn.edu, cbegg@seas.upenn.edu
Personal Email: carolinembegg@gmail.com
Phone Number: (203) 400-0930
GitHub Username: carolinebegg
Open an issue on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>Markdown Cheat Sheet Ⓜ️⬇️</title><link>https://carolinebegg.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/page/markdown-cheat-sheet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://carolinebegg.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/page/markdown-cheat-sheet/</guid><description>Markdown Cheat Sheet Hugo has excellent Markdown support out of the box. By default, Hugo uses the Goldmark Markdown processor which is fully CommonMark-compliant. See the configuration instructions to learn more about the extensions you can configure.
Overview You can refer to the table below for an overview of basic markdown syntax:
TASK MARKDOWN SYNTAX Heading 1 # Heading 2 ## Heading 3 ### Italics *italics* Bold **Bold** Strike ~~strike~~ Blockquote &amp;gt; Links [link name](https://link.</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://carolinebegg.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://carolinebegg.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/privacy-policy/</guid><description>Privacy Policy TLDR: We do not use cookies and we do not collect any personal data.
Website visitors No personal information is collected. No information is stored in the browser. No information is shared with, sent to or sold to third-parties. No information is shared with advertising companies. No information is mined and harvested for personal and behavioral trends. No information is monetized. Information we collect and what we use it for The server hosting this site can collect the following information:</description></item></channel></rss>